But you have to look up “vancale”
This is your kind of thing
Because,  in Milano, If you go to the really expensive stores, like me... nah
haha, okay.
Okay.
There's a place in Calabria that makes these.
Vancale, never heard of it
Flowers!
You have flowers
Yeah.
It’s beautiful here, it’s windy on our side
Actually, it could be heard on the Sea
Nice.
It's warm, huh? Such a difference
We live in a different world
I mean, the wind on a day like to day makes a difference
So if it was windy here the air is cool
Yeah, but now it’s a lot nicer
I'll put this on your side
I won’t have any
You’re not a meat eater
No, I eat meat, but not today
And it is the Holy Week
Which is not...
There is no obligation.
And what do you do for Easter?
For Easter, it will be nice and quiet and,
celebratory.
so you’re here? I’ll be here yes
I also have other
bread that is a bit hard.
Oh no, grissini is perfect
we have lentil soup and
it's rich. And I put some oats in there, so.
Oh, wow,
a thick stew.
I've been eating it for weeks, haha
Oh, really?
I mean, not this particular batch.
Oh, we'll have to stove on for sure.
Still well into May
I mean,
if we have cold days in April or May,
even on this side... but you do it a lot less, right?
But actually now, as long as it is
still sunny, I get away with it.
But if it's not sunny in April
or May of maybe ten degrees.
Yeah,
I sometimes use more wood in that change period
than in
winter, but it's not really,
because the sun is... the passive...
Yeah.
like today, now it's just like 20
degrees inside, just from the balcony.
these grapes have a cherry kind of taste
but it grows, like a bush
This is a... melo cotogna (quince)
The brother of our melo cotogna
Oh, this is a nice stairs
Yeah. Progress
It's not done yet.
but I’ve been sliding enough
This is whatever you call these.
It’s going to be warm.
Warmer?
Yeah. Oh, no.
This is? garlic, no
Onion
Oh, wow... do you smell the lemons?
Oh. Oh, my God, I never see this
Oh, it's very intense.
Beautiful.
And they’re blossoming
And these are the oranges over there
on the left side.
So this, this has been a bit said.
This was pretty, but it brings so many flowers
I have to take off.
There's still one
lemon down there. Oh. Hi, lemon.
Smells amazing.
It is a beautiful...
It's a very intense smell
While this is coming, slowly,
this will be very.
I mean, this has put in a lot of,
a cut them very, very,
dramatically
because they were up on the roof
but, they, these with, these are the,
the pineapple guavas that I love
so much. They are ripe in December.
I don't know when you were here.
Okay. If you want to try?
I don't remember, but it's, it has a
it tastes like a lemon sorbet.
Quite wonderful.
This.
Is a the last tomatoes, or the only tomatoes
It’s still freezing.
In the nights, so I have to wait with the stone work
I think there's two more cold days.
It's very sunny, though.
But, yeah.
-3ºC or so during the night.
So I'm going to clear out the cabin
and then work on the wall
sa soon as it’s a bit warmer
there’s a... if you want to make a sandwich
Hummus.
Cheese.
Mayo
A lot of mayo, nice.
Cut down this raspberry patch for the first time
for a year, it was nothing.
But now there was a small forest growing,
too much for us to eat.
And, they're very invasive.
And these are the shoots of...
like the brown ones are from last year.
They'll give fruit early in the season.
So late spring.
Then there will be new shoots as well.
They'll give fruits end of summer,
basically.
Like in September or so.
So that's still enough for us to eat.
The birds don't eat them very much.
But we like them, so
But it was getting too big
so this is overseeable
Ciao raggaze
ciao
The white one is beautiful.
She grew!
You think so? she was already big
The Jimny is back on the grid
It's got Italian plates now.
What's the first car I came here with.
It has been serving me well, but
the last year it was,
not really in use.
So it’s going to be Ela’s car
doing groceries, and being more independent
She’s doing laundry.  Usually
we do this in town in a machine.
But on a nice day like this,
we can do it here.
In a beautiful spot,
Little cabin under a big  rock
actually, Ela found it last year
when she was camping up there
for her birthday.
She spent the morning here.
It's one of the many places
just around here
where you can just hang out for an hour
or so.
It's really peaceful.
This beautiful chestnut tree
Yeah.
I'm finishing
the outer walls of the workshop.
The inside I have to do.
I think it's a day's work
or 2. Two days work.
And then I'm going to start doing
the floor.
I'm already configuring the workshop.
How it's going to be laid out with,
the tools.
I think it's all going to be around
a central island, with a table saw,
I'm going to get a new table saw
with a cast iron top and, a better motor.
So because all the work
I'm going to do from now on has to be...
a level up, basically. Most of the work was stone work
and more rough carpentry work,
you know, roof construction,
but the next phase will be making doors
and windows.
There’s going to be two doors
in second cabin,
three actually, downstairs and two upstairs.
Three windows there
The front door of the first cabin I will redo
because it's very weak door.
Furniture, tables, probably.
So there's a lot I'm going to make
for the cabins
and the workshop.
For that, I just need better tools.
I've been waiting with investing in tools
because everything rusts.
All my tools that are in a second cabin.
Because the roof is still open,
the doors and windows are open
It's always very humid inside.
And, it makes your tools rust,
especially after 4 years here.
So first,
I have to make the workshop
weather proof properly.
That means I have to have a door
and the window, and then I can put
something like a saw table with a cast
iron top,
something which rusts very quickly in there.
But sort of a central island with a table saw
together with a workbench with two vises,
for hand woodworking,
making joinery,
and then next to it, an outfeed table.
So that's basically going to be
one big flat space where I can work on
space to walk around.
And then against the walls, cabinetry
on one side,
a jointer planer to make wood flat,
probably some dust collection as well.
A wood stove is going to be in there.
And all the cabinetry
is going to have like doors and drawers,
but it's going to be on the same level,
like 90cm high or so.
It makes it comfortable to work on everything at the same height.
And then the miter saw
is probably staying outside at this point
under the little roof.
It's actually quite a good space
for the tools.
It doesn't rust as much
there as inside the cabin
because it's it's outside,
the sun shines there,
and it's also protected from the humid air that comes in the night up from the valley.
and a miter saw inside, it's going
to take up a lot of space, so
but yeah I'm going to slowly collect
a bandsaw probably as well
I think I can use that.
I saw some beautiful
old saws on Marketplace.
So I'm going to be hunting
some old Italian tools
Because they're a well built cast
iron heavy tools
that just stay good forever.
Probably need to polish up
some blades and bearings and
clean it up and whatnot.
So yeah,
that's going to be an exciting phase.
Just slowly building up the workshop and,
so that's going to be, well,
the week after next week.
I think next week
I have some guys coming over to help
with the spring clean up.
Basically.
Because this is the last week
before it's really starting to turn green
and it's a good time to do some forestry
work,
clean up the roads
and, to make some space.
There's a lot of branches
and cut off things from cutting trees.
And we need to clean up.
So that's what we'll do next week.